alwaysgirls.com 2002-12-08

# Always Girls

**Always Girls** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [Always Girls](http://www.alwaysgirls.com/)

**Advertisers**  
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**Personal Information**   
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

**External Links**   
This site contains links to other sites. Always Girls is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Special Relationships**   
_(** Special relationships are often very confusing, as the collection of information is often seamless to the user. Because you indicated that there are special relationships, such as "Powered by" partners, content providers, business partners, cobranded sites, then these relationships must be addressed in your privacy statement. These relationships need to be clearly defined and it must be clear who owns the information, who is receiving the information collected by the site and who has access to this information. It must be clear what type of information is shared. Is only select information shared? Is the sharing of information limited to only aggregate information? **)_

**Contacting the Web Site**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [webmaster@alwaysgirls.com](mailto:webmaster@alwaysgirls.com)
